Welcome to our first practical video on QA. Over the next couple of videos, we're going to focus on setup.
And the first piece of setup is that we need an API key. And we're going to use the OpenAI.
So let me just Google OpenAI API. And this is an overview. We need to come to platform.openai.
You need to log in. Creating an account is absolutely free, but you do need to log in in order to get an API key.
Let me log in for myself. And I'm going to show you how to generate an API key.
Overall, it can still happen that you have a free tier. That's definitely a possibility.
But overall, what we're going to do throughout this course is not going to cost you more than one US dollar.
With the caveat that the minimum that you can do is like five US dollars for credit.
But it seriously is less than one US dollar. And okay, let me figure this one out as I always lose myself here.
Because this platform is just getting bigger and bigger. And okay, I would say dashboard.
API keys. And then to create an API key, you click on create. Let me name it as, you know, AI agent.
And I'm just going to give it all permissions. It should be your account as well. So this should be okay.
Now it's very important that you copy this. This is going to be the last time that this is shown.
It's just here once. So you need to copy and store it as a secret somewhere.
And for us, in case that you have not, I would encourage that you download the AI agents folder.
And we go to crew AI job interview prep part one. And we're going to click on new more and then Google
Collaboratory. And from here we can kick it off. And what I'm going to do here, I click on copy.
And like I have already quite a bit, but let me add another secret here. You can see that I have been
working on this. Let me, I'm going to call it AI agents, open AI. Right. So this will be a key that
I'm going to use specifically for this course. I do control V to paste it here. And let me in a sense
hide it here. And then the last piece that one would do. So you click here and this is going to
get here the code in order to get a specific API key. And for instance, I would come here, AI agents,
open AI and I would store it under something. So let's say open AI, API key equals to this open
AI API key. And let me just add here. So we'll focus it on setup. And the very basic of things
would be okay. Contra enter and let me come here to secrets at the same time. Currently it's
connecting to the script, but you see here notebook access. It's not what is happening is that all of
these secrets, they're passed from one notebook to the other, but you do need to activate for that
specific notebook. In this case is going to prompt you grant access, which you come to grant access.
And then I can see I took way too long. It's okay. I do control enter and here we go. So now we have
the open AI API key, which is absolutely ready to go. And with this, I'm going to stop this video.
Let me just give it a title here. So crew AI job interview prep part one. Here we go. And that is
it. So I'll see you in the next video.